good afternoon,
добрый день
here I am asking people from Russia how
вот я у людей из россии спрашивать как
do you feel about the war in ukraine
вы относитесь к войне в украине
which one is happening in ukraine now
которой сейчас происходит на украине
I don’t understand look yes it’s forbidden for you
не понимаю смотри да у вас это запрещено
to call it a war
назвать войной дать
you support your Ukrainian troops
поддерживаете вот ваших войск украины
, but I like the fact that
поддерживает но мне нравится то что
civilians are dying,
гибнут мирное население
that is, it turns out you support the
то есть получается ты поддерживаешь
killing of this civilian population, we
убийство это мирного населения мы тебе
don’t like it so
это не нравится так
I support my boys who
я поддерживаю свой своих пацанов которые
are dying there, I don’t support it, and the trouble is
там гибнут я не поддерживаю и беда то
that civilians are dying there,
что там гибнет мирное население одеваешь
but you dress  look, imagine that your
но смотри вот представь что вот твои
boys from the yard went to the next yard
пацаны с двора пошли в соседний двор
to beat and there they beat some kind of grandmother, that
бить и там бабку бьют какую то еще то
is, you support your boys with
есть ты поддерживаешь своих пацанов у
you, you can’t help your grandmother suffers
тебе ты не подержишь у бабка страдает
so it turns out
так получается
to answer correctly
правильно
look and not morality enter war
смотреть и не мораль энтерите война
war in any case everyone  trying to
войной в любом случае каждый пытается
grab himself a piece of something the right
отхапать себе кусок чего-то правильная
run in it is wrong we are not
пробега в ней неправильно мы не
going to grab  a piece of russia no you
собираемся отхапать кусок россии нет вы
and you're not going to just if you
а вы не собираюсь просто если вы ваш
didn't read your present ass of water victories
презент не читал свою жопу воды побед
it would be all right but what about his
было бы все нормально а что с его пятой
ass by chance but for some reason a
точке случайно а почему почему то
man why this special operation started like this
человек почему так началась это
well because someone in the
спецоперация ну потому что кто-то в
Kremlin is like that  decided to give the order, but you didn’t
кремле так решил отдал приказ а у вас не
decide, but we didn’t attack you
решили но мы не нападали на вас
as long as
покуда
we wanted to place a neighbor opposite us,
хотели разместить напротив нас соседом
your president
ваш президент
wanted to place weapons near the neighbor,
хотели разместить около соседа оружия
and which one is now
надо и которая вам сейчас
supplied to you by drognin and
поставляемого drognin и
how would you choose your country, how would you react,
своей страны как бы вы отреагировали а
but look,
вот смотрите
I’m just how much I  I know I may not
я просто насколько я знаю я плохо может
know geography well, but the Baltic countries Estonia
знать географию но страны балтии эстония
and Lithuania, Latvia, they are already in NATO and no closer
и литва латвия они уже в нато и не ближе
to Moscow than Ukraine,
к москве чем украина
tell me what kind of real estate, what is your name,
скажите мне какого недвиж как вас зовут
Andrey, were convicted, let's
андрей в осудили давайте на карту
see this sweden map, Andrey Andrey,
посмотрим эту sweden карту
listen why the date tried to place
послушай почему дата пыталась разместить
on the border  what weapon to
на границе свое оружие для каких
look for and firstly she hasn’t
смотреть и во-первых она еще не
posted anything yet we don’t have a NATO base
размещала ничего у нас нет базы нато так
so but this is a
но это ну-ка сновидения не нет вот нет
dream  we don’t have experience yet, we want
в попытке еще нет мы мы хотим нет ни
no, we want to join NATO and be a member of
было мы хотим войти в нато и быть членом
NATO, that’s what we want, that’s our right,
нато вот что мы хотим это наше право вот
look,
смотрите
to defend yourself from Russia, in
чтобы защищаться от россии на
fact, you are now how is your
самом деле ты сейчас как у вас идет
deponia going, why is Ukraine in the country in
deponia почему на стране украины по всем
all this conflict  they don’t forgive us
вот этим конфликтом они нам не прощают
smoked
курила
when russia posted it yes it was like that
когда россия разместила да было такое
look i just i just can’t understand
смотри я просто я просто не могу понять
japan there are claims against you yes
японии есть к вам претензии да потому
because you took their territory you
что вы забрали ихнюю территорию
still haven’t signed
до сих пор не подписаны
russia why don’t you look at your
россию почему вы не посмотрите свои
actions
действия
let’s not attack
давайте так на нас не нападал
us like that let’s  let's attack ukraine to kill
давайте нападем на украину убивать
or the
или
score will be so guys let's make up
счете будет так ребята давайте давайте
your mind
вы определитесь
let's make up our minds somehow so
давайте мы как-то определимся так
all the same why start this war
все-таки из-за чего же эта война начать
because they wanted to place weapons here
из-за того что тут оружие на то хотели
or
разместить или
for the
ради
sake of what you are after all  they came here for the sake of the
ради чего вы все-таки сюда зашли за ради
biolaboratory so for the sake of the rocket there
биолаборатории так ради там ракетно то
for the sake of the donbass and
ради донбассе и
I went
я пошли
guys I joked about the laboratory lobby
пацаны я пошутил про лобби лаборатория
I didn’t think I know that aunts are there
не думал я знаю что тетки такие там
screaming grandmas gap laboratory thought  you
кричат бабки пробел лаборатории думу вы
don’t believe in such a thing, really believe in it, and
не верите в такое реально в это верить и
where in Ukraine there were laboratories for you,
где в украине были тебе лаборатории
everything is gone, so
все пропал так
it’s not me for
это не я
you in Ukraine, you were chapter 3 and tricks of
тебе украине были тебе главе 3 и трюков
evil to the button so it
ли зла до кнопочки так
doesn’t work for a long time
не получается долго знаем испил
wing 5
ролики двоится дочь под крылом 5 поспел
was forged so and you set specific
ковалась так и ты задаешь там конкретный
nutrition there and I really drove the pipe of the
питание и я реально погнал трубе
laboratory I didn’t think that these boys would
лаборатории не думал что эти пацаны
push the pipe to the pipe Labradors will sound like
грудь задвигать трубе лабрадоры зазвучат
amethyst pensioners grandmothers where the
аметистом пенсионеры бабушки там где
spirits are so for the gypsies well and from the corner
духи так за цыгане ну и из угловые
cult still
культовыми таки
from the color type slaves and here are the baths and believe
от цветотип рабами и вот ванны и верить
the necks sang the sides of the ribeye, not something confirmed there,
шейки спела борта рибай не что-то там
that is, there every nu lan
подтвердил то есть там каждым ну лан
confirmed and .  where he
подтвердила и . где
will tell me this is how everything is known to
скажет меня это вот так все ведома
hide in Chernihiv to stand and the
скрывать в чернигове стоять и
biolaboratory what to strain there in
биолаборатории че там напрягать пит
Donetsk and here the food publishing house and the
донецком и вот издательство питания и
finger is not stretched to the button
пальчику не вытягивается до кнопочки
it was argued by the moon and you can’t do
было аргументировано луны а ты не можем
this in it doesn’t want hysterical welding was
этому в не хочет истерика сварка был
near the cruise it was similar to so methodical
около круизном похож на так методичный
actions  as a psychologist and a psychiatrist
акций как психолог и психиатр
, we pack and know these features and on the video
пакуемся знаем и так этих фич и на видео
I will add glory to Ukraine
я добавлю слава украине